<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DB Demo</string>
    <string name="thumbnail_content_des">Thumbnail</string>
    <string name="shop">Cửa hàng</string>
    <string name="home">TRANG CHÍNH</string>
    <string name="product">SẢN PHẨM</string>
    <string name="categories">CỬA HÀNG</string>
    <string name="menu">menu</string>
    <string name="cart">Giỏ hàng</string>
    <string name="back">Quay lại</string>
    <string name="search">Tìm kiếm</string>
    <string name="call">call</string>
    <string name="user_field">Email</string>
    <string name="password_field">Mật khẩu</string>
    <string name="sign_in_button">Đăng nhập</string>
    <string name="sign_up_button">Đăng ký</string>
    <string name="sign_in_suggest">Đã có tài khoản?</string>
    <string name="sign_up_suggest">Chưa có tài khoản?</string>

    <string-array name="label">
        <item>Helmet</item>
        <item>Goggles</item>
        <item>Grenade</item>
        <item>Optic</item>
        <item>Med kit</item>
        <item>Carrier</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="description">
        <item>A type of protective headgear that is specifically designed to protect the wearer head from ballistic threats such as bullets and shrapnel. These helmets are made from materials that are capable of stopping or deflecting bullets and other ballistic threats.</item>
        <item>Emergency response personnel use tactical eye wear to protect their eyes when working in the field. Common hazards that responders use tactical spectacles and goggles to protect against include shrapnel, blunt objects, chemicals, and blood and other biohazards.</item>
        <item>An explosive weapon typically thrown by hand (also called hand grenade). A modern hand grenade generally consists of an explosive charge ("filler"), a detonator mechanism, an internal striker to trigger the detonator, an arming safety secured by a transport safety. </item>
        <item>These scopes extend the standard engagement range for troops in ground combat and usually have lower magnification levels. They have simple reticles that help you acquire targets quickly at a close to medium range.</item>
        <item>Dressings and bandages (gauze role, sterile gauze pads, eye pad, roll of adhesive tape, elastic bandage for sprains, sterile cotton balls and swabs) Over-the-counter medicine for cuts, burns, and injuries. </item>
        <item>A type of body armor system designed to hold ballistic plates, which are inserted into pockets on the front and back of the carrier. These plates, typically made of ceramic, steel, or composite materials, offer protection against bullets and other ballistic threats.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>